---

- question: "What are entities?"
  tags: [tactical]
  answer: "Entities are often mutable (though not of necessity) objects that are unique even when their values correalate to objects of the same type (in contrast to a value object)."

- question: "What are the dangers of over-abstracting?"
  tags: []
  answer: >
    - The language of the abstractions does not match the language of the model.  This language will creep into the user domain.
    - Makes it difficult to model the individual types
    - Leads to a complex heirarchy and special cases
    - An excessive amount of code because you're trying to solve an unsolvable problem and attempting to solve future needs that are unknown

- question: "What are some examples of entities and why?"
  tags: []
  answer: "asdfadf asadf"

- question: "What are some examples of value objects and why?"
  tags: []
  answer: "fizz buzz"

- question: "What are the steps/rules to creating a right-sized aggregate?"
  tags: []
  answer: >
    1. start off by designing small, cohesive aggregates by creating one entity per aggregate and making it the root.

- question: "What are the rules of Aggregate design?"
  tags: []
  answer: >
    1. Protect business invariants inside Aggregate boundaries
    2. Design small Aggregates.
    3. Reference Other Aggregates by Identity Only
    4. Update Other Aggregates Using Eventual Consistency

- question: "Describe the first rule of aggregate design"
  tags: []
  answer: "foo 1"

- question: "Describe the second rule of aggregate design"
  tags: []
  answer: "foo 2"

- question: "Describe the third rule of aggregate design"
  tags: []
  answer: "foo 3"

- question: "Describe the fourth rule of aggregate design"
  tags: []
  answer: "foo 4"

- question: "Describe the fifth rule of aggregate design"
  tags: []
  answer: "There's only four rules"
